downeu.com 2011-08-30

# Privacy Download - DownEU

****By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Downeu.net. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, Downeu.net may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

 **Downeu.net** is committed to protecting your privacy. Downeu.net does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. Downeu.net will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
We use ClickHype and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

 **Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

 **Modification of Privacy Policy**  
Downeu.net reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.

 **Use of Information**  
Downeu.net will not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission. Downeu.net uses users’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally.

Using e-mail addresses provided at forum registration or otherwise, Downeu.net may periodically sends out e-mail updates as form of newsletters to our users. Users can indicate that they do not wish to receive e-mail information from Downeu.net.

Although Downeu.net does not specifically seek to obtain any information from minors, this website is open to all. We urge children to use our website only after they have discussed it with their parents.

Downeu.net generates search results automatically from databases and any search may return unexpected or unwanted references. These references may contain offensive, obscene, or illegal material. Because Downeu.net merely links to and does not publish content supplied by third parties or which is generally available on the Internet, Downeu.net has no editorial control over such information. Please use this site and any material referred on it responsibly.
